Hey guys, I just found a wonderful tool.
>> [music]
>> What I just did, I put in this my
product into the tool and I found the
output right away. So the photographs
are for my Amazon listing. It generated
for my primary photo as well as all the
secondary images with all the details.
I just wanted to also create 360° view
of my this product and look at the
output. It's amazing. Same way I also
tried with Amazon A+ content and also
the 360° photo shoot. All without
writing any prompt. So you now know it's
not the AI model, it's all the AI
agents. So if you want to know how I did
it, let's [music] quickly dive in and
see how you can also do the same. So
first let's go to the tool's website.
You can find the tool's link in the
description. So click on it and once you
click on it you can find a sign up page.
So you can sign up using your Google
account.
Once you sign up, you can see the
dashboard.
>> [music]
>> In the middle you can see the prompt box
where you can just put down
any kind of topic and how would you like
to generate [music]
your video with.
And you can click on video. You can see
there are so many different options
[music] like advertising studio,
dynamic captions, lyrical video, create
short videos, make explainer videos
using your script it generates video and
you can
>> [music]
>> clone yourself and create your own
avatar.
You can see here.
So this tool is famous for its AI
>> [music]
>> agents. So let's see.
Here it says agent and models. So you
can see so many different agentic models
are available. Then you can see directly
generative models means all the top AI
models are available
>> [music]
>> here. So same way you can also check out
about trending topics and videos. If you
want to explore different workflows, you
can check it out here and you can also
explore how the different people has
generated
different videos using [music] these AI
agents and models.
So for us let's go back to agent and
model and click on advertising studio.
So you can see currently it is free for
few weeks. So you can try it out as much
as possible right now. Now you can see
on the screen they are providing
automatically preset means this tool has
already generated multiple of agents. So
each agent does their job and you get
your right output. Same way
>> [music]
>> you can see the presets are about brand
mood board, Amazon [music]
A+ content, thematic photography,
catalog photography, back shot 360,
[music] Amazon primary image, secondary
image, 360 product video, hero shot,
[music]
mock up generator and mock up billboard.
So now let's start with the one preset
which is Amazon A+ content.
>> [music]
>> So let's see.
So once you click on it, it asks you to
generate your project. So I have already
generated mine which is advertising
studio.
>> [music]
>> I'm just going to click on it. So once
you create your folder, [music] you can
see at the bottom there is a prompt box.
And I already selected Amazon A+
content. So the automatically written
prompt or brief is here. So what I need
to do, I just need to attach my image.
And so I'm just going to online [music]
and I decided to take these shoe as my
product. So I just downloaded all the
images into my laptop. So I'm just going
to upload one of them. So I uploaded my
shoe image. [music] So at the bottom
there are some setting part. So if you
click on here, it automatically
selected. You can change the screen
size, the number of images you're
looking for. Keep the unlimited on.
Amazon A+ content is already selected
and hit on unlimited.
>> [music]
>> So this is the beauty of agentic AI.
Let's say if you are going to any real
advertising agency, you just go there
and brief about your requirements. You
say like I need a entire photo shoot of
my product in this [music] way. This is
my theme, this is my product, this is my
logo. So after taking all the brief from
you, [music] a director goes to the art
directors and art director decide what
kind of prompts they want to use [music]
and how they want to take the entire
photo shoot. After that, the
photographer comes and take multiple of
photos and goes to the editing team and
then [music] the final output a client
receive. These agentic AI [music] knows
their job and do the task as per
>> [music]
>> their setting.
So what we get directly is the final
output. So this is different than AI
model. This is not AI model only, this
is AI model plus AI agents. So you can
see the final output on the screen.
Looks amazing, right? With all [music]
the different details.
Now if you want to make any changes to
these details, you [music] can do
directly from here. You see on the right
side at the bottom, it says edit [music]
using comments. So once you click on it
and you can say
add
the pricing [music]
$45
to my image.
Or in better word, product image.
[music]
Now it will take some time.
Now you can see our edited image
>> [music]
>> on your screen. So fast, so accurate.
Now I just wanted to add some more
information. So [music] I just tried
something new here where I added
>> [music]
>> the description where I put it down more
information like I want to add the
material [music] price and more thing
about the product. And within few
seconds you can see [music]
it has completely changed my A+ content.
So now you see how easy to get [music]
the right kind of image. So let me try
one more use case where
I'm just going [music] to use
instead of Amazon A+ content, let's try
with the thematic [music]
photography. So I just selected thematic
photography and you can see automatic
[music]
brief has been added. I can attach two
images. So [music] I'm just uploading
quickly
a image of my
product which is a purse. So again I
just downloaded these images from one of
the online store.
After that everything else looks [music]
good. So I'm just going to click on
unlimited. It's that easy.
So now you can see the final output of
our product on your screen.
>> [music]
>> The agent has did their job well and
added a lot of props
>> [music]
>> and provided us a nice thematic image
with our product. At the bottom right
side you can see you can edit the same
image using comments. You can attach the
same image to the prompt and you can try
to you know create the video. So [music]
on, you can up scale this image and
download from here. So now we are going
to check the next preset which is
[music] Amazon primary image and
secondary image. So if you have gone to
any Amazon
product page, you can see the first
image of the product has nothing but but
just a good quality photograph of entire
product. And if you go to the next next
to next images, you can see
the secondary images where you can see
the product in details [music] along
with lot of details. You can see on the
screen. So if you want to generate this
kind of
>> [music]
>> high quality Amazon product listing
primary and secondary images, you can
use this tool and currently it is free
so you can try as many time as possible.
Let's go back and try
for one of our product. So you can just
click here at the bottom thematic
[music] photography and then scroll down
and click on primary image.
Now you see our
brief is already there and now let me
select one of the image.
>> [music]
>> So I'm just going to select
this product image. [music] Once the
product is uploaded, I just want to
create two images for
>> [music]
>> this product. So you can see if you want
to generate two images simultaneously,
you cannot use the unlimited part.
[music] But that's fine, let's try the
generate. So now you can see our Amazon
product listing primary image is ready
and you can [music] see the clarity of
image. So the same way you can create
multiple of secondary image and and you
can upload to your Amazon product
listing. So [music] now you we tried
like couple of
their presets. Now let's try one more
which I wanted to try which is
uh [music]
360 product video. Because I always like
to watch the video where it is showing
the product into 360°. I already tried
[music] some AI models, but this one is
different because it has the agent which
can understand [music]
and do the different task and just give
us the final output.
So let me try with 360 product video
preset.
So once you selected, you see the prompt
has already been generated which is very
simple. And here my same shoe image is
attached which I'm going to remove it
and this time I'm just going to add
[music] a
outfit image. So I have already
downloaded image from my online store.
Now uploaded all my images.
>> [music]
>> So let's see how does it generate. I'm
just going to click on unlimited.
So now we have to wait for few seconds
and I'm really excited to see
>> [music]
>> how does it come up. So you can see the
final output with 360° video
on the screen. You can download it and
you can upload to your product listing.
>> [music]
>> So I just wanted to try something real
because these are all images I taken
from online store [music] and they might
have already gone through the proper
photo shoot of product.
>> [music]
>> So what I did I just like take taken the
photograph of my mic and its box. And
[music]
let's try this one and see how good it
is with [music] this kind of raw photos.
So what I'll do
uh let's go to the trend and
>> [music]
>> go to advertising studio and I just
wanted to try with let's say Amazon
primary image feature. [music]
Let's see how good it is with my
original product. So I'm selecting one
image. Okay, so I'm I have uploaded my
product box image. Let's see how good it
is with Amazon primary image.
>> [music]
>> I'm just going to hit on unlimited. I'll
just let's wait for few seconds and then
we have our final [music] output. So now
you can see the final output of my
product Digitek on the screen.
So I just want to use my same
>> [music]
>> mic product with the back shot 360 which
is the different preset. It has the four
photo upload option. So I'm just going
to select my case [music]
and the box image. So you can see all of
them I have attached.
So I can hit on unlimited. So it's not
letting me create [music]
using unlimited so I'll just use my
credit. Let's see.
So now you can see my final photo
with [music] 360° view with my mic
Digitek. If I compare with the original
photos,
>> [music]
>> it did much better job. So that's the
beauty of AI gents. So now let's try my
this shoe with the product 360° video.
Let's try right now and see how is the
output. [music]
So I'm just going back to my preset
selecting the product video and
I have a multiple
>> [music]
>> photo upload options where I'm just
going to upload as many
photos as possible and I have only four
photos so I just uploaded and then I can
hit [music] on
generate.
Now look at the 360° product view of
[music] my shoes. It's amazing. You can
see from all the different angles. I
love the output
of all the different presets. So we
tried a lot of different photos. We
[music] used from
online listing and we also tried with my
own product which [music] is available
right now here. And you can see it has
generated good quality accurate images
>> [music]
>> much faster. The beauty is you don't
need to write the lengthy prompt. You
just need to give the brief as you are
telling any
>> [music]
>> marketing or photography agencies and
it's doing fantastic job. So I hope you
learn how you can create your product
photo shoots for listing on Amazon or
listing on your websites or for
different marketing purpose. So if you
learn something new
>> [music]
>> from my this video then make sure you
hit like button, subscribe my channel
and share this video with your
e-commerce friend. See you in the next
[music] one.